Hello.
In this lecture, we're going to go over how to export our game to get started.
You're going to go to edit and go to product settings, then go to maps and modes and go over to game
default map.
This game default map represents the first level that the player is going to see when they open up your
game.
We want this to be our main menu map, so select the main menu map and if you want you can change the
editor start up map.
This is going to be the first level that you see when you open up your Unreal project.
But now we can leave this at level one or you can change this to be another level if you want to.
We can close this and we are now ready to export our game.
Next, before we export our game, you may need to install Visual Studios.
I'll showcase a video now showing you what components of Visual Studios you need to install.
I think we need to install the game development with C++ and the Visual Studios installer, and when
you install with your studios, you want to make sure that you get to individual components and that
you have the NET SDK installed.
So let's look for NET here.
You should make sure that you've installed this NET SDK.
I didn't have this installed and when I tried to export my product, it basically had nothing inside
of it.
Okay.
Once you've installed those parts, you can go to platforms for Windows and select shipping.
Bingo platforms Windows and Go Package project.
It will ask you where you want to package your project.
I'm going to package mine on my desktop.
Just go select and then it'll begin to package your project.
Okay, so it looks like my project to export.
Let's go to show up at Lock to see what is wrong.
So it says the following files are set to be staged but contain restricted folder name Apple.
Okay.
I checked what this error means and I think we're not allowed to name this folder Apple because of the
company.
Apple.
So we need to find this folder and just rename it something else.
It's kind of silly, but let's just do it.
I have a folder called Apple, so if I go to my Warrior animation folder, I made this file called Apple.
Let's just rename it.
And call it.
Red fruit.
And we can then right click on our content folder to fix up redirects, go save and hopefully it will
package and export this time.
I'm just going to restart my Android engine project.
Okay.
So hopefully it exports this time.
I'm going to go platform's Windows package project.
I'll select my desktop.
And let's see.
Okay.
So it looks like that was the issue my project has exported.
Once you export your project, it should be in this photo called Windows.
Now, if I double click and open this up, I should be able to play my game.
So it says to the action platformer I can go start.
And let me click on level one.
And know take me to level one.
I kind of cheated and put myself at the end, but I can go back and explore this level if I wanted to.
That's all for this course.
I hope you enjoy it.
If there are any more topics that you want me to cover, I can update this course later with the suggestions
of the viewers.
That's all.
Okay.
So I'm now going to go back in this project and comment all the blueprint and remove all the line traces
and boxes.
That way you can download the completed product and see everything if you want to.